

## Whoami

I'm a computer systems engineer with more than 6 years of experience, I had work with clients of many different business areas. Think about myself as a Full Stack Developer because I feel very comfortable working on backend and frontend, and also on DevOps. Through all of my professional experience I have been exposed and worked in diverse environments and people and I have been collaborating on develop, design, and deploy of applications and web systems with different design patterns, languages and technologies such as:

MicroServices, SPA applications, Rest API's, GraphQL API's, Mobile Hybrid Apps, Javascript, Ruby, Python, Java, SQL Databases, No-SQL databases, etc.

## Information

**Mobile:** +(52) 55 2084 0226

Email: vh.urquides@gmail.com

Location: México

Github: TORVICK

Skills		
NAME	STATUS	COMPLETION
Ruby on Rails	Expert	99% ———
₽ JS	Expert	90%
JQuery	Expert	90%
AngularJS	Medium	60%
Phyton	Medium	50%
nede NodeJs	Medium	70%
ReactJS	Medium	60% ———

SO's Mobile

NAME STATUS COMPLETION NAME STATUS COMPLETION

macOS MacOs	Expert	99%	_	React Native	Medium	60%	
⚠ Linux	Expert	99%	_	<b>A</b> AppCelerator	Medium	50%	
■ Windows	Expert	99%		PhoneGap	Medium	50%	_
DevOps				DataBase (SQL/NoS	QL)		
NAME	STATUS	COMPLETION	N	NAME	STATUS	COMPLE	TION
aws AWS	Medium	50%		Postgres	Medium	80%	_
◆ Docker Docker	Medium	50%		₩s& MySQL	Medium	80%	
Heroku	Medium	65%		SqlServer SqlServer	Medium	50%	_
DigitalOcean	Medium	50%		4 mangeodi MongoDb	Medium	75%	
⚠ Linux Servers	Medium	50%		<b>ॐ</b> reds <b>Redis</b>	Medium	70%	
Webservers & Other	tools						
NAME			STATUS		COMPLETI	ON	
NGINX			Medium		80%		
Apache Apache			Medium		80%		
ApiRest			Expert		90%		
<b>∵</b> Soap			Medium		80%		
			Medium		50%	-	
			Medium		80%	_	
Education							
INSTITUTE			PROGR.	AM	ST.	ATUS	DATE
Tecnológico Nacional TecNM	onal de México		Compu	uter Systems Engineer	CERT	TIFICATE	2016
Employment							
Uulala 2019-2021 Server Administra	tor/Developer FullSt	ack					
EasyMePresta 2018-2019 Server Administra	tor/Developer FullSt	ack					
Metricas SAPI de C							

2017-2018 Developer FullStack



OPENCAP

2016-2017

Developer FullStack



Dirección General de Centro de Formación para el Trabajo (DGCFT)

2015-2016

Developer BackEnd